https://www.stingray.co.za/terms-conditions

info@stingray.co.za +27(0) 21 442 1540
0Item(s)
0 Items View Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Bathroom & Kitchen
Bathroom AccessoriesBathroom ScalesMirrorsKitchen AccessoriesKitchen ScalesKitchen StorageBinsLaundryCleaning ProductsStorageCooking
Home, Health & Pets
StorageWater HeatersMirrorsLightingTV BracketsPetsHealthGarden
Bathroom & Kitchen
Bathroom AccessoriesBathroom ScalesMirrorsKitchen AccessoriesKitchen ScalesKitchen StorageBinsLaundryCleaning ProductsStorageCooking
Home, Health & Pets
StorageWater HeatersMirrorsLightingTV BracketsPetsHealthGarden
Terms & Conditions
Product was successfully added to your shopping cart.
Go to cart page
Continue
Terms & Conditions
A. Privacy Policy
All STINGRAY websites (hereinafter referred to as “the/this website”) and the services therein, are offered to you, the User, by Stingray Accessory Manufacturers (Pty) Ltd and is situated at 5 Beach Road, Woodstock, Cape Town, its subsidiaries and/or related companies (hereinafter referred to as “we”, “our”, “us”, “STINGRAY” or “the Company”) subject to the following terms and conditions. These website terms and conditions must also be read with the Protection of Personal Information Bill (“POPI”) and Consumer Protection Act (CPA).
1. Privacy, Access to and use of information a) The website receives various types of information from Users who access the website, including Personal Information as detailed in the Protection of Personal Information Bill            (“POPI”).b) STINGRAY voluntarily subscribes to the protection of Personal Information principles, and complies with the requirements of POPI.c) STINGRAY is fully aware of the Consumer Protection Act, and complies with the requirements of the CPA.d) The website may electronically collect, store and use Personal Information of the User, as provided by the User such as name, contact details and any other Personal Information      provided by the User to the website through any online forms, polls, surveys, questionnaires or competitions as provided for on the website from time to time.e) Any correspondence between the User and the website will be retained for record purposes.f) In the event that the User applies for a seminar, registers or enrols via the website, Personal Information relating to the registration will be collected in order to process the User’s    application, registration or enrolment.
2. Consenta) By using the website and/or submitting Personal Information, the User consents to:    i. the collection, collation, processing, and use of its Personal Information which includes but is not limited to full name, physical address, cellular and/or telephone numbers, email       address, age and gender;    ii. the transfer of your Personal Information to countries outside South Africa;    iii. the disclosure of your Personal Information to entities that are related to STINGRAY;    iv. that your Personal Information may be retained by STINGRAY for an indefinite period, subject to your rights to have the Personal Information removed.b) Receiving promotional and/or marketing material and information in any form, which you can opt out of at any time.c) In the event that the User of the website is under the age of 18 years, consent must be provided by a parent or guardian before Personal Information may be provided by the User     to the website. If we become aware that Personal Information relating to a minor has been collected without parental or guardian consent, such Personal Information will be     removed from our database. Age verification checks may be performed when required.3. Interception of communicationsa) Despite the best efforts of the website and of STINGRAY, it is possible for internet-based communications to be intercepted:    i. without the use of encryption, the internet is not a secure medium and privacy cannot be ensured and as a result internet email is vulnerable to interception and forging; and    ii. STINGRAY will not be responsible for any damages the User or any third party may suffer as a result of the transmission of confidential or disclosed Personal Information that you         make to STINGRAY through the internet, or that you expressly or implicitly authorise STINGRAY to make, or for any errors or any changes made to any transmitted Personal         Information.b) To ensure acquaintance with and awareness of the privacy measures and policies of STINGRAY, the User is urged to take care to read and understand the underlying privacy     clauses incorporated in this Policy.
4. Privacy
a) Casual Surfing
i. The User may visit the website without providing any Personal Information.   ii. The User accordingly grants express written permission for the website servers in such instances collecting the IP address of the User computer, but not the email address or any       other distinguishing Personal Information (“non-identifiable information”).  iii. This type of non-identifiable information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent at the website, pages visited, etc, but will not be linked to you.  iv. STINGRAY uses this non-identifiable information to determine the use of the website, and to improve content.   v. STINGRAY assumes no obligation to protect this type of non-identifiable information, and may copy, distribute or otherwise use this type of non-identifiable information.   b) Unsolicited Information    i. If the User posts unsolicited content or other Personal Information to the website and does not indicate otherwise, the User grants to the owners a non-exclusive, royalty-free,        perpetual, irrevocable and fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute and display such Personal        Information throughout the world in any media.   ii. The User grants to STINGRAY the right to use the name that the User submits in connection with such Personal Information, if they choose.  iii. The User warrants:       1. that the User owns or otherwise controls all of the rights to the Personal Information that the User posts;       2. that the Personal Information is accurate;       3. that by the supply of the Personal Information to STINGRAY the User does not violate this Policy and does not infringe the rights of any person or entity; and       4. that the User indemnifies STINGRAY for all claims resulting from the receipt by STINGRAY of the Personal Information the User supplies to it.   iv. STINGRAY may monitor and edit or remove any Personal Information where posted to public pages. STINGRAY takes no responsibility, and assumes no liability for any Personal        Information posted by the User or any third party.   c) Solicited Personal information the user gives to the website    i. STINGRAY requires certain Personal Information necessary to facilitate some of your interactions with the website and STINGRAY. As a result of your interaction with STINGRAY        some of your Personal Information may be obtained and retained, which may include but not limited to, your gender, national origin, age, language, educational information,        identity number, email address, physical address and telephone number.   ii. STINGRAY will only use your personal information as it becomes necessary for the purpose of providing you with relevant service, product, property and industry related        information, and you hereby consent to STINGRAY obtaining, processing, and retaining your personal information. Your information will be retained until you request STINGRAY        to delete any personal information which may be held by STINGRAY.  iii. The User’s Personal Information will not be used for any further purpose other than providing you with the relevant service, product, property and industry related information        and/or providing you with information relating to STINGRAY.  iv. The User’s Personal Information may be used to build a profile of the user to form the basis for the User’s interaction with the Website.   d) Promotional Information
STINGRAY aspires to provide you with updated information about new services, products, seminars and relevant property and industry information. In each instance, the User is     provided an opportunity to opt-out of such information circulars. For more information, please call STINGRAY’s Call Centre, or send an email to info@stingray.co.za outlining your        request.   e) Business Transfers        i. STINGRAY may enter into business arrangements and its customer base is one of the more valued assets. In such an event, customer Personal Information will be one of the        transferable assets.   f) Lawful Disclosure      When STINGRAY is served with due legal process requiring the delivery of Personal Information, it has the legal duty to abide by that demand, and will do so. STINGRAY may also    impart Personal Information if permitted or required to do so by law.   g) Surveys and statistical purposes     i. STINGRAY understands that efficiency and customer care translates to good service. STINGRAY may periodically conduct online customer care surveys to enable the updating         of our offering to you.    ii. When it conducts a survey, STINGRAY must inform the User how the Personal Information gathered will be used, and provide the User with the opportunity to opt-out from such         surveys.    h) Storage and security     i. Personal Information will be stored safely. Personal Information will be destroyed and deleted once it has become obsolete (out of date or unusable).    ii. STINGRAY takes the safety, security and confidentiality of your Personal Information very seriously and will take all reasonable technical and organisational measures to prevent         any loss of, damage to, unlawful access to or processing of your personal information.     i) Your Rights         i. You rights include asking us not to process your Personal Information for marketing or any other purposes. To inform us of whether or not you want to receive marketing or other         communications, simply indicate your consent preferences when you provide us with your Personal Information or at any future time by emailing us at info@stingray.co.za    ii. You also have the right to access Personal Information held about you by emailing us at info@stingray.co.za. We will send you the Personal Information held by us within the         appropriate legal time limit.   iii. You rights also include the ability to request us to update your Personal Information that we have collected or stored to ensure accuracy and also to request that we delete any of         your Personal Information we hold.   iv. STINGRAY will not use your Personal Information for any other purpose other than what has been outlined in the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.5. Intellectual Property Rights           a) The copyright to all content on this website including applets, graphics, images, layouts and text belongs to us or we have a licence to use those materials.      b) All trademarks, brands and logos generally identified either with the symbols TM or ® which are used on this website are either owned by us or we have a licence to use them.           Your access to our website does not license you to use those marks in any commercial way without our prior written permission.      c) Any comment, feedback, idea or suggestion (called “Comments”) which you provide to us through this website becomes our property. If in future we use your Comments in           promoting our website or in any other way, we will not be liable for any similarities which may appear from such use. Furthermore, you agree that we are entitled to use your           Comments for any commercial or non-commercial purpose without compensation to you or to any other person who has transmitted your Comments.      d) If you provide us with Comments, you acknowledge that you are responsible for the content of such material including its legality, originality and copyright.6. Disclaimers    a) The information we provide on this website is of a general nature only. We are not providing professional advice and you should obtain professional or specialist advice that is         appropriate to your circumstances and we give no warranty and accept no liability should you use the information without obtaining independent advice.    b) We give no warranty that the information is free from error or omission and you should use your own care and skill when accessing and using it.    c) To the extent permitted by law, any condition or warranty which would otherwise be implied into these terms and conditions is excluded.    d) We take all due care in ensuring that our website is free of any virus, worm, Trojan horse and/or malware, however we are not responsible for any damage to your computer         system which arises in connection with your use of our website or any linked website.    e) From time to time we may host third party content on our website such as advertisements and endorsements belonging to other traders. Responsibility for the content of such         material rests with the owner of that material and we are not responsible for any errors or omissions in such material.7. Indemnity
By accessing our website, you agree to indemnify and hold us harmless from all claims, actions, damages, costs and expenses including legal fees arising from or in connection     with your use of our website8. Jurisdiction    a) These terms and conditions are to be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of South Africa and any claim made by either party against the other which in any         way arises out of these terms and conditions will be heard in South Africa and you agree to submit to the jurisdiction of those Courts.    b) If any provision in these terms and conditions is invalid under any law the provision will be limited, narrowed, construed or altered as necessary to render it valid but only to the         extent necessary to achieve such validity. If necessary the invalid provision will be deleted from these terms and conditions and the remaining provisions will remain in full force            and effect.9. Use of the information    a) We shall only use the Information as provided for in these terms and conditions, and in terms of the website, and shall only release to the chosen entities that are related to         STINGRAY, certain types of Information provided by the User.10. Amendments      a) We reserve the right, within our sole discretion and at any time, to amend these terms and conditions, which includes deleting any terms and conditions and adding any further                terms and conditions.      b) The amended terms and conditions will immediately and automatically come into effect.      c) The amendments will be binding on the User and will immediately and automatically form part of these terms and conditions, subject to the above option to terminate.11. Updates
The User hereby undertake to ensure to keep all Information updated and current and acknowledge and accept that all entities that are related to STINGRAY, shall immediately       have access to all such updated Information should they so require.12. Accuracy of information     a) We do not guarantee the accuracy of any Information which is found on this website, therefore the User should not assume that the Information on the website is always current          or accurate, and other sources of this Information should be consulted before making any decision to act on the Information displayed on this website.     b) The User hereby agrees to provide only accurate Information.     c) The User will remain liable to any third party for the inaccurate Information furnished by the User and we, as the provider of the medium to display and make the information           available, will not be held liable to any third party regarding the content of the User’s Information.13. Fees      There are no fees charged to the User, who willingly makes use of the website and/or the services herein.      Transacting on our website constitutes a legal transaction between two willing parties. Your rights are protected by the CPA and we in no way limit these. However please be       aware of the warranty procedures and policies that govern these transactions, as specified below:
Delivery Charges      Delivery charges may be applicable for your online order. All orders to a value of less than R400 incl. VAT or deliveries to outlying areas will attract a delivery surcharge. This         amount will always be disclosed prior to your order being finalised. Delivery charges are variable and Stingray reserves the right to requote delivery on a processed order. Should       the delivery charge change, Stingray will contact you and you will have the right to cancel the order and receive a refund in full (based on your original method of payment). Should       you accept the additional charges, payment may be made using payfast as in the original transaction.
It is your responsibility to ensure that the correct delivery address is provided during the ordering process – any additional delivery costs due to wrong or incomplete addresses will            be for your account. This applies to packages considered undeliverable (when there is no answer at provided address, or no-one authorised to accept the delivery) too.
PLEASE NOTE:           Delivery options only refer to business days, therefore an express overnight on a Friday will only arrive on the Monday.
Next day delivery is only applicable to orders placed before 12.30pm on a given day
All orders marked for collection at our Cape Town Branch can only be collected once you have been notified telephonically or by email.
Any orders placed after office hours will only be processed on the following working day.* The above points do not apply to weekends and public holiday
14. Availability of website and service      a) The availability of this website and the service may become unavailable from time to time due to maintenance, electricity supply failure, network problems or for any other           reason.      b) STINGRAY shall not be held liable for any interruptions in the availability of the website and the services, for any reason.
Product Availability and stock outs          Due to the nature of our business we cannot guarantee that every transaction concluded on the website will have suitable stock available. We aim to be in stock of every item           listed, however practically this isn’t always possible.
Stingray will contact you in the instance of an item not being available and you will have the choice to either wait for replenishment stock (quoted in the correspondence) or            receive a full refund, matched to your original method of payment.
How your order will be processed          Order processing will begin as soon as we have confirmed payment, whose processing time is out of our control. We aim to process and despatch your order within a working           day of payment confirmation.15. The user's privacy            a) We acknowledge that the User has the right to privacy and privacy of the Information provided, and we respect this right.      b) We shall use our best endeavours to protect the User’s Information and to keep it confidential from persons who are not authorised to have access to and view the Information.16. General Disclaimer
The User hereby agrees to access and use this website entirely at its own risk.        By opening an account on the www.stingray.co.za website / online shop, I consent that the personal information I am providing is voluntary, specific and informed17. Exclusion of liability         a) The website and all content on the website is provided on an "as is" basis, and we make no representations or warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, to the           accuracy of the contents on the website. We do not warrant that the functions and services provided by the website will be uninterrupted or error-free, or that the website or the           server is free from viruses or other harmful components.       b) STINGRAY, including the owners, directors, employees, officials, suppliers, agents and/or representatives shall not be liable for any loss or damage, whether direct, indirect or            consequential, or any expense of any nature whatsoever, which may be suffered by the User, which arises directly or indirectly upon reliance of the website and/or its content.       c) STINGRAY, including the owners, directors, employees, officials, suppliers, agents and/or representatives shall not be responsible for any direct, indirect, special, consequential            or other damages of any kind whatsoever suffered or incurred by the User related to its use of, or its inability to access or use, the content or the website, the services, or any            functionality of the website or of any linked website.       d) The User hereby indemnifies us, and our owners, directors, employees, officials, agents, suppliers or representatives, and keep us fully indemnified, from and against any loss             or damages suffered or liability incurred in respect of any third party, which arises from the User’s use of this website and/or the services.18. Intellectual property rights       a) STINGRAY is the owner of this website and the contents thereof and we retain all intellectual property rights thereto, whether registered or not, including all current and future            content on the website, which is not owned by a third party, and nothing in this website should be construed as a right to use or licence of any of the intellectual property.       b) The website and its contents, which includes all intellectual property therein, may not be reproduced, copied, used, sold or displayed in any manner whatsoever, without our             express prior written consent thereto.19 Links and linking     a) We provide the User with links to other websites through this website. The fact that we have such links must not be construed as constituting any relationship or endorsement of          the linked third party and the reliance on any Information and content provided by the external link is entirely at the User’s own risk.     b) We may at times, display third party advertising and promotional material on this website and the display of such material should not be construed as us endorsing or creating          any relationship between us and that third party. Reliance on any such promotional or advertising material is entirely at the User’s own risk.     c) If a third party wishes to link to this website from their website, they must first obtain our express prior written approval and permission.20. Termination and suspension      a) We may, in our sole discretion decide to discontinue with the service provided in this website and may terminate the website itself, at any time whatsoever and the User shall           have no recourse in any event of termination.      b) We may, in our sole discretion decide to suspend the service provided in this website and website itself, at any time whatsoever, and the User shall have no recourse in any           event of suspension.21. Good Faith
The User herewith agrees to use this website and the services herein with the utmost good faith, integrity and trust.      Returns, Warranty and refund policy.      All Stingray products are warranted to be free of manufacturing defects for a period of one year from date on invoice. Some products, in exceptional circumstances, carry a 2 year       to 10-year warranty.
Returns will only be accepted once contact has been initiated with our service department on 0860 100 2582 or info@stingray.co.za
Faulty products within the warranty period can be returned at our cost, for repair and if unsuccessful, replacement
Should a purchased product not operate as intended or be classified faulty within 14 days from receipt, Stingray will cover collection and redelivery costs of your item. This does       not cover wilful neglect and failure to follow instructions.
After 14 days but still within the warranty period, should you wish to return your product, delivery costs will be for your account. If the product is faulty Stingray will repair or replace       the item and redeliver the item at Stingray’s cost – as fast as possible. Should Stingray be unable to repair or replace, you will be refunded the initial cost if the item in question as       per your invoice.
Goods delivered that are unwanted may be returned for a refund within 5 business days from date of delivery. All returned goods must be returned in their original packaging       (undamaged), and unopened.
These goods will be subject to a 25% handling charge. Delivery costs will in no way be refunded. The costs of returning unwanted goods will not be for Stingray’s account.22. Governing Law
This website is owned and operated within the Republic of South Africa. We, as well as the User, hereby agree that these terms and conditions shall be governed and construed in       accordance with the laws of the Republic of South Africa.23. Complaints and Disputes
Any complaints or disputes can be sent through to us via the “Contact Us” links on the website or via info@stingray.co.za24. Entire Agreement           a) This Website is controlled, operated and administered by Provider from its offices as set out below within the Republic of South Africa.      b) If any of the provisions of these Terms are found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid or unenforceable, that provision will be enforced to the maximum extent           permissible so as to give effect to the intent of these Terms, and the remainder of these Terms will continue in full force.      c) These Terms constitutes the entire agreement between the Provider and the User with regard to the use of the Content and this Website.
*“User/s” means the person who chooses to insert their personal Information on the website, which Information is to be distributed and the terms and conditions herein apply to              the User, as the context indicates.
**“Information” means any personal details which the User provides in any way through the use of this website, in any form whatsoever, which includes but is not limited to its              names, postal and physical addresses, contact numbers, e-mail address and name of employer and any other type of personal Information as defined in POPI, each of which              forms a separate data tag of Information on the website
Head Office: Cape Town
5 Beach Road, Woodstock, Cape Town, 7925, South Africa
Johannesburg Office:
Unit 2, Cedar Wood Office Park, Cnr. Western Service & Mount Lebanon Road, Woodmead, South Africa, 2144
Office Hours:
© Stingray 2020. All Rights Reserved. Ecommerce by Stock2Shop.com
